冬青枝条装点大堂
<i>Deck the halls with boughs of Holly.</i>
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
又到了这个季节
<i>'Tis the season...</i>
嗨
Hi!
嗨  唱的不错  邓肯阿姨
Hey, sounding good, Mrs. Duncan.
哦  这必须的
Oh! I know.
今晚我演唱的效果会更好
It's going to sound even better when I sing it tonight
在每年一度的圣诞夜邓肯达人秀上
at the annual Duncan Christmas Eve Talent Show.
哦  妈妈  我和斯宾塞也要唱歌
Oh, mom, Spencer and I are singing too.
我们还一起谱写了首圣诞新歌呢
We even worked out a new Christmas song together.
哦  这太棒了
Oh, that is so wonderful!
敢跟我今夜同台共嗨  勇气可嘉
And so brave of you to sing the same night I do.
嗯  我们要去超级圣诞乐园了
Well, we're off to Super Christmas Land.
哦哦  超级圣诞乐园  那是啥
Ooh, Super Christmas Land? What's that?
哦  超级冒险乐园就是这么改名字的
Oh, that's what Super Adventure Land calls itself,
圣诞时期叫一个礼拜超级圣诞乐园
for one week each year at Christmas time.
上周是超级光明节乐园
Last week it was Super Hanukkah Land.
下周将变成超级宽扎节乐园
Next week it's Super Kwanzaa Land.
圣诞快乐  大伙儿
Merry Christmas, everybody!
哦  奶奶来了
Oh, grandma's here!
-吔  -哦
- Yay. - Oh!
哦 哦
Oh oh!
查莉  见到奶奶该说啥
Charlie, what do you have to say to grandma?
拜拜
Good-bye.
抱歉  她只是太激动了
Sorry, she's just excited.
因为我们要给她去拍  第一张和圣诞老人的合影了
We're off to have her very first picture taken with Santa.
我懂
I understand.
好吧  嗯  我们要走了  但等不及要再见到你了
Okay, well, we gotta run, but we can't wait to see you later.
-哦  好吧  -好吧
- Oh, good. - Okay.
-好吧  拜  -拜
- All right, bye. - Bye.
哦  艾米  见到你太高兴了
Oh, Amy. It's nice to see you.
哦  琳达  见到你很高兴
Oh, Linda, it's nice to see you.
嗯
Well.
装饰得不错的啥玩意儿
The decorations look nice and whatnot.
尽管花环摆错地方了
Although that wreath is in the wrong place.
放那挺好
I like it there.
我一会儿给挪了
I'll fix it later.
好吧  鲍伯
Okay. Bob?
-哦  我的神啊  -妈妈
- Oh, my goodness! - Mom!
（注：海格力斯是希腊神话中大力士）
这是我的儿子还是海格力斯
Is that my son or Hercules?
哦  妈妈  得了吧
Oh, mom! Please!
减点脂  增点肌  无需大惊小怪
Dropped some weight, got totally buff.Don't make a fuss.
嗯  航班如何
So, how was the flight?
哦  老样子  还是延迟啥玩意儿的
Oh, you know, the usual delays and whatnot.
但飞机上大家都喜欢
But everybody on the plane loved the song
我今晚在达人秀上要唱的歌
that I'm going to sing at the Talent Show.
冬青枝条装点大堂
<i>Deck the halls with boughs of Holly...</i>
哦  哇哇哇哇  等等  孩子他奶
Oh, whoa whoa whoa whoa!Hang on there, grandma.
我要唱装点大堂
I'm singing "Deck The Halls".
甜心  也许在你装点之前应该先把大堂清扫一下
Sweetheart, maybe you should clean the halls before you deck them.
除大堂之外我可能还会“装点”下别的东西哦
I may deck something besides the halls.
好的  别激动
Okay, stand down.
我们不能同时都唱这首歌  我可从菲尼克斯赶过来的
We both can't sing the song and I did come all the way from Phoenix.
她可是从菲尼克斯赶过来的
She did come all the way from Phoenix.
-好吧   但这是我家  -这是她家
- Well, it's my house. - It is her house.
-是我生了你  -是我嫁了你  咋地
- I gave birth to you. - I married you. Ba-bam!
行了  够了
Okay, fine!
谁都不唱  这是我的最终决定
Nobody sings it. That's my final decision.
哦  你的决定
Oh, that's your decision?
世上没别人了  轮得到你来主宰达人秀
Who died and made you King of the Talent Show?
-真不假  -难以置信
- Really! - Unbelievable.
吔  圣诞节
Yay, Christmas.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Crazy王  Focus
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof.</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I survived.</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice.</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right.</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down.</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around.</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who you turn out to be.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第二十集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E20  A Duncan Christmas
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys?
嗯  听着  我需要个小忙儿
Uh, listen. I need a favor.
嗯  既然我们仍处于圣诞节前要好好表现阶段
Well, since we're still in the pre-Christmas gotta-be-nice zone.
有什么能为你效劳的
What can we do for you?
我要你们搞明白你妈今年给我买什么礼物
I need you to find out what your mom got me for Christmas.
-为啥  -嗯  因为
- Why? - Well, because.
每年  我和你妈都约好
Every year, your mom and I,we make this agreement
在对方礼物上不要花费太多  可是
not to spend too much on each other's presents but...
我从来不懂那是啥意思
I never know what that means.
我本以为“别花太多钱”
I would have thought "not spending too much"
是你掌握最熟练的口头禅
is a phrase you're very familiar with.
每年都以弄错收场
Every year I wind up getting it wrong.
哦  是的  就像去年她给你买了个
Oh, right, like the time she bought you
很不错的表  你却给她个
really nice watch and you got her those...
- 呃  叫什么来着   -鞋袜
- Uh, what were they called again? - Slocks.
不是拖鞋  也不是袜子
They're not slippers, they're not socks.
而是鞋袜
They're Slocks.
就是那年老妈老是滑得东倒西歪
That was the Christmas that mom kept slipping and falling.
鞋袜  他们不仅丑陋  还很危险
Slocks... they're not just ugly, they're dangerous.
好了  拜托  伙计们  嘿
All right. Come on, guys. Hey...
当你们打探你们的礼物时
When you were doing your present snooping,
有没有恰巧听到你妈要送我什么
did you happen to see what your mom got me?
老爸  我都大了  早就不干这行了
Dad, I'm older now.I don't do that anymore.
还有谢谢耳机啊
And thanks for the headphones!
嗯  调皮的帮不上忙  看看听话的吧
Well, naughty can't help me.Let's try nice.
-哦哦  是我  -哈哈  PJ
- Ooh, that's me! - Ha ha, PJ!
拜托  查清楚你妈要送我什么
Come on, find out from your mom what she got me.
-好吧  我会跟她谈的  -好的  太棒了
- All right, I'll talk to her. - All right, great.
她对你会全盘托供的  我们都知道你是她的最爱
She'll tell you anything. We all know you're her favorite.
是他
He is?
嗯嗯  嘿嘿嘿  我可没说我的最爱啊
Well, hey hey hey! I didn't say my favorite.
是泰迪  是吧
That would be Teddy, right?
无可奉告
No comment.
哦  没事
Oh, relax.
我保证你会进前五的
I'm sure you're in the top five.
我知道你又累又饿还冻脚
I know that you're tired and you're hungry and your feet are cold,
但发牢骚不好用
but all this whining doesn't help.
但这也太久了吧
But it's taking so long!
什么时候我才能见到圣诞老人
When do I get to see Santa?
很快的  我保证
Really soon, I promise.
是啊  只要那小孩能下得了圣诞老人的膝盖
Yeah, if that kid would ever get off Santa's lap.
他都在那顶上呆了有10分钟了
He's been on there for like 10 minutes.
是啊  咋那么长时间
Yeah, what's taking him so long?
只要坐下  许个愿  按快门  闪人
It should be sit, list, snap, go.
坐下  许个愿  按快门  闪人  这能有多难
Sit, list, snap, go! How hard is that?
圣诞老人听到了  小姐
Santa can hear you, young lady.
耶  嗯  我就是这个意思  圣诞老头
Yeah, well, that's kind of the idea, Santa.
但说真的  你还是冷静下来比较好
But seriously, you might want to cool it, all right?
-凯尔这家伙不咋地  -等等  你认识圣诞老人
- Carl's not the nicest guy. - Wait, you know Santa?
是的  我们以前在这工作过
Yeah, from when we worked here.
我俩演过“致敬美国”
I did a show with him."The tribute to America".
（注：将苹果引进美国的人）
没变肥之前他扮演的可是苹果佬乔尼
He played Johnny Appleseed before he put on the weight.
圣诞老人也听到这个啦
Santa heard that too.
-嘿  妈妈  -嘿
- Hey, mom. - Hey.
干嘛呢
What you doing?
焊接工程
Welding.
嗯嗯  好好
Good good.
嗯  是这样  我在想该给老爸买什么圣诞礼物
So, listen, I was thinking about what present to get for dad.
我可不想跟你买的一样了
And I don't want to get him the same thing you did.
你要送他啥来的
What did you get him again?
是你爸叫你过来刺探我要给他买啥吧
Did your dad send you down here to find out what I got him?
接下来要说啥我还没准备呢
I'm not prepared for any follow-up questions.
你别想知道我要给他买啥
I'm not going to tell you what I got him.
那我就不问了
Then I won't ask again.
我还是你最喜欢的吧
Am I still your favorite?
这就是为啥你是我最喜欢的
That's why you're my favorite.
太棒了
Yes!
嗯  那你就继续忙乎你的焊接活吧
Well, then I'll let you get back to your welding.
-好消息  各位  -你搞明白你妈要送我啥了
- Good news, guys. - You found out what your mom's getting me?
没  但我确定了我是她最喜欢的
No, but I confirmed I'm her favorite.
嗯  又来这一套
Well, there you go.
又要毁了圣诞节
Gonna fail Christmas again.
也许我能帮上忙
Maybe I can help you.
你已经给妈妈买礼物了  是吧
You already bought mom a gift, right?
我猜在某个鞋袜区买的
And I'm guessing it's somewhere in the Slocks area?
事实上  我买了个特别的海绵毯子给她在厨房用
Actually, I got her a very special foam rug for the kitchen.
洗碗时她可以站在那上面
Something she can stand on when she's doing the dishes.
叫做脚踏垫
It's called the foot cush.
哦  看样子你想重现鞋袜时期的美好时光
Oh, so you want the Slocks to seem like the good old days.
哇  老爸  你这门槛已经够低了  难以置信这都跨不过
Wow, dad, you set the bar so low, I can't believe you went under it.
-精辟  -谢谢  彼此彼此
- Good one. - Thank you. I like yours too.
伙计们  我已经尽量深思熟虑了
Guys, I'm just trying to be thoughtful.
听着  有一次你妈在商店里看到一个脚踏垫
Look, your mom saw a foot cushion in a store once,
她说她想要一个
and she said she might like one.
好了  现在你已经买了个便宜的礼物
All right, so the point is you got the cheap gift covered.
现在你要做的就是再给妈妈买个贵的礼物了
Now all you have to do is buy mom a nice gift.
给她买俩礼物
Buy her two gifts?
完全正确  把它们藏在两个不同的地方
Exactly. Then hide them in different places
当你拆开老妈给你的礼物时
and after you open mom's gift to you,
你就知道该给她哪个了
you'll know which one to give her.
盖比  你太有才了  嗯
Gabe! That's genius. Eh?
这才像样  这就是为啥你是我最喜欢的
There you go. That's why you're my favorite.
整个争宠事件越来越没意义了
This whole favorite thing is starting to lose all meaning.
太棒了  下个该我们了  查莉
Yes. We're next, Charlie.
泰迪  看
Teddy, look.
一小时后回来
Back in one hour?!
你不能这样
You can't do that.
抱歉小姐  我每工作4小时  休息1小时
Sorry, missy, I get a one hour break every four hours I work.
协会制度
Union rules.
-什么工会  -假演协
- What Union? - H.A.G...
假日演员协会
The Holiday Actors Guild.
别别  等等  拜托  拜托
No no, wait. Come on, come on.
看啊  我们已经在这等两个小时了
Look, we've been waiting here for two hours.
并且  我们又饿  又累
Okay, we're hungry, we're tired...
找协会讲去  别挡我道
Take it up with H.A.G. now get out of my way.
你别想走  圣诞老头
You're not going anywhere, Santa.
来试试
Try and stop me.
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha!
哦哦
Whoops!
哦  泰迪
Oh, Teddy.
太棒了
Yes!
快来照相  我按住圣诞老人的手
Let's get the picture.Here, I'll hold Santa's arms down.
离开那个肥仔
Step away from the fat man.
好啊  好啊
Well well well.
这不是泰迪·邓肯吗
If it isn't Teddy Duncan.
你好  警长
Howdy, Sheriff.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas.
你们重新装修了  效果很好
You redecorated. Place looks good.
想让它有点节日氛围
We try to give it a holiday feel.
-嘿  亲爱的  -哦  鲍伯
- Hey, honey. - Oh, Bob?
嗯  我决定达人秀上不唱“装点大堂”了
Um, I've decided I'm not going to sing "Deck The Halls" at the Talent Show.
真的  哦  谢谢
Really? Oh, thank you.
谢谢你为和谐社会所做的牺牲
Thank you for taking the high road and keeping the peace.
我的节目要改为表演一场模仿秀
I'm going to do an impression instead.
-模仿秀  -嗯哼
- An impression? - Mmm.
模仿一位家庭成员  你猜是谁
Of a family member. Can you guess who?
我大老远的从菲尼克斯飞过来的那啥玩意儿
"I flew all the way in from Phoenix and whatnot".
还有  哦哦
And, oh oh!
鲍伯真壮那得啥玩意儿
"Bobby is so muscley and whatnot".
哦  嘿  妈妈  嗯  你听到多少
Oh. Hey, mom. Um, how much did you hear?
啥也没听到
I didn't hear a thing.
我只是来宣布我决定
I just wanted to tell you that I've decided to
今年让艾米来唱“装点大堂”
let Amy sing "Deck The Halls" this year.
嗯  我很高兴终于有人理解圣诞精神了
Well, I'm glad somebody understands the true spirit of Christmas.
我的节目改为表演模仿家中一位成员
Instead I'm going to do an impression of a family member.
哦
Oh.
猜猜是谁
Can you guess who?
我的家真埋汰  咋地
"My house is dirty". Ba-bam!
我连个花环都挂不好  咋地
I can't even hang a wreath. "Ba-bam!"
-啥玩意儿  -咋地
- Whatnot. - Ba-bam!
- Whatnot! - Ba-bam!
噢  别吵了  说实在的  真受够了你们俩这样
Oh, come on. You know what?  I've had it with the two of you.
算了  达人秀部分取消了
Forget it. Talent Show is canceled.
他以为他是谁  他不是你儿子么
- Who does he think he is?  - You gave birth to him.
是是  他不是你老公么  咋地
Well, you married him. Ba-bam!
去年你半路阻截超级冒险乐园园长
So last year, you tackled the Super Adventure Land Mayor.
今天你用雪球袭击圣诞老人  下次准备做什么呢
Today you bowled over Santa Claus. What's next?
复活节你是不是打算用鱼叉刺兔子呢
You gonna harpoon The Easter Bunny?
呃  不知道  我还没想好复活节干点啥
Well, I don't know. I haven't made my plans yet for easter.
我还得在这儿待多长时间
How much longer do I have to stay in here?
在我们审理之前你哪都不能去
You aren't going anywhere till we have a trial.
法官来之前呢  我们也不会审理
Can't have a trial till the Judge gets here.
呃  那法官什么时候来
Well, when will that be?
超级冒险乐园圣诞期法庭开审了
Super Adventure Land Christmas court is now in session.
圣诞老人  上庭
Santa?
真没想到我的休息时间会这样度过
This is not how I wanted to be spending my break.
泰迪·邓肯  你可以靠近陪审员了
Teddy Duncan, you may approach the bench.
终于啊
Finally.
关于原告卡瑞戈和被告邓肯一案的审理
In the case of Kringle versus Duncan,
你被指控用雪人头袭击他人
you are charged with assault with a snowman head.
你有什么要申辩的
How do you plead?
因为无罪  所以
Not guilty by reason of being...
无罪
Not guilty.
那好  圣诞老人  你来讲下  当时的情形是怎样的
All right, Santa. In your own words, tell us exactly what happened.
嗯  我只是按规定的时间去休息  接着她就袭击我
Well, I was taking my H.A.G. mandated break and then she attacked me.
不信你问他  他当时在场
Ask him. He saw the whole thing.
呃  法官阁下  我拒绝出庭作证
Uh, your honor, I have to recuse myself.
我和被告处于一种超乎寻常的亲密关系
I'm in a very happy and committed relationship with the defendant.
噢  我的甜心
Ooh, Sweetie.
谢谢  甜心  你可以回避了
Thank you, Sweetie, you are recused.
好了  我们再来听听被告的描述
All right, let's hear from the defense.
法官阁下  要我说  圣诞是一年中最为欢乐的时刻
Your honor, if I may, Christmas is the most magical time of year.
而谁最喜欢这个时候呢
And who loves it more than anyone?
是孩子
The children.
我所做的不过是想让一个孩子开心
And I was just trying to make one child happy.
如果那也叫犯罪的话  那好  叫我罪犯吧
So if that's a crime, well, then call me a criminal.
最好不要  呃  不管怎样让我快点离开这儿就行
Or don't. You know, whatever gets me out of here faster.
情况我已经完全了解  我准备宣判了
I've heard enough. I'm ready to rule.
我的裁决是  有罪
My verdict is guilty.
耶
Yes!
是你有罪
You're guilty.
我  我  这又不是在审讯我
Me? I'm... I'm not on trial here.
我一直就对你不满  凯尔
I've never liked you, Carl.
是时候你该学点圣诞精神了
It's time you learned a little something about Christmas spirit.
我罚你和这个小女孩合张影
I sentence you to one picture with this little girl.
谢谢你  警长
Thank you, Sheriff.
耶
Yay.
来点生气  凯尔
Jolly it up, Carl.
小家伙你干什么  在往哪看呢
What you doing? What are you looking at?
在看什么啊
What you doing?
噢  噢  他简直像个甜美的小天使
Oh. Oh, he's such a sweet little angel.
呃  那还用说
Aw, he sure is.
他人生的第一个圣诞节就充满争吵和不快真是太糟糕了
It's too bad his first Christmas has all this fighting and unpleasantness.
我也这样觉得
I know.
我有个办法
I have a solution.
是我帮你收拾东西给你送行吗
I'll help you pack.
我是打算提议我俩可以一起唱装点大堂这首歌
I was going to say that we should sing "Deck The Halls" together.
你的意思是合唱
You mean as a duet?
嗯  那  我们合唱吧
Yes. So, let's du-et.
耶  让我们请神奇的波比尼和他的助手查莉下场休息
Yeah! Let's give it up for the great Bobbini and his assistant Charlie!
波比尼  请问一下
Okay, quick question for Bobbini.
你变不见的那只鸽子  到哪去了
That dove you made disappear? Where is it?
噢  别担心  宝贝儿  我们待会儿会找到它的
Oh, don't worry, honey. We'll find it later...
希望如此
Hopefully.
好了  呃  紧接着  老妈和奶奶献上合唱
Okay, well, up next, the musical stylings of grandma and mom.
冬青树枝装扮大厅
<i>Deck the halls with boughs of Holly.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
圣诞季节带来欢欣
<i>'Tis the season to be jolly.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
穿上我们华美的衣裳
<i>Don we now our gay apparel.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la.</i>
唱着古老的圣诞颂歌
<i>Troll the ancient yuletide carol.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
周围满是浓重的圣诞节日氛围
<i>See the blazing yule before us.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
弹起竖琴  噢
<i>- Strike the harp...  - Ow!</i>
大家一起歌唱
<i>And join the chorus.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
跟我一起为节日祝福
<i>Follow me in merry measure.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la la la la la.</i>
我会说出什么是你的圣诞礼物
<i>While I tell of yuletide treasure.</i>
发啦啦啦啦啦
<i>Fa la la la la la.</i>
啦啦啦啦
<i>La la la la!</i>
刚才  你们欣赏了
Well, there you have it,
奶奶和老妈第一次同台表演
grandma and mom working together for the first and
或许也是最后一次
probably the last time.
好了  接下来我们请PJ和盖比上场表演  你俩要表演什么
Okay, next we have PJ and Gabe doing... what are you guys doing?
即兴剧场独幕剧
An exercise in improvisational theater.
说的对  即兴即最佳  伙计们
That's right. Improv at its finest, people.
我们想观众给来点建议
We are looking for suggestions from the audience.
我们需要人物和道具方面的建议
We need an occupation and an object.
律师和岩石怎么样  建议必须是警察和香蕉
- A lawyer and a rock.  - Has to be a cop and a banana.
警察和香蕉  好建议
- A cop and a banana.  - Excellent suggestion.
噢  警察我来了
Oh, here I am being a cop.
噢  看那
Ooh, look at that.
有根香蕉
A banana.
我在剥香蕉皮
Now I'm peeling the banana.
嘿  我是抢劫犯  把香蕉交出来
Hey, I'm a criminal. Give me that banana.
不  这是我的香蕉
No, it's my banana.
谢幕
And scene.
好吧  接下来斯宾塞和我将为你们带来一首新作的圣诞歌曲
Okay, now Spencer and I are going to sing a new Christmas song for you.
希望大家喜欢
Hope you like it.
我听见教堂的钟声响起
<i>I hear church bells a'ringing.</i>
唱诗班空灵的声音在回荡
<i>Carolers are singing.</i>
我和谐融入其中
<i>Harmony with me now.</i>
你看上去是如此动人
<i>You are looking so lovely.</i>
耶
<i>Yeah!</i>
即使灯火阑珊
<i>Even if the lights go out.</i>
在炉火的微光中  我们在槲寄生枝下亲吻
<i>We've got mistletoe, and firelight.</i>
在这寒冷的冬夜
<i>On this cold December night.</i>
户外的雪创设如此情调
<i>The snow outside will set the mood.</i>
当我为你唱我写的歌
<i>As I sing my song for you.</i>
哇噢
Woo!
圣诞快乐  托比
Merry first Christmas, Toby.
耶
Yay.
这是送给盖比的
For Gabe.
好的  圣诞快乐  盖比
Okay. Merry Christmas, Gabe.
嘿  耳机啊  谢了  老爸老妈
Hey, headphones! Thanks, guys.
你怎么知道里面是什么  你打都没打开
How do you know what's in it? You haven't opened it yet.
呃  说的是哈
Oh, right.
嘿  耳机啊  谢了 老爸老妈
Hey, headphones. Thanks, guys.
好了  你妈的礼物在哪
Okay, where are mom's presents?
贵的那个在红色的圣诞树下  便宜的那个在我椅子后面
Expensive one's under the red tree, cheap one's behind my chair.
好了  宝贝儿  该我俩交换礼物了
Okay, honey, time for you and I to exchange presents.
但我想你先把礼物给我
But I want mine first.
行  等下  不吃亏的货
Well, hang on there, tiger.
小心  小心  好了  我们来看看里面是什么
Easy easy. Okay, let's see what we've got here.
噢  我的天啦
Oh, my goodness!
哇噢
Whoa.
大盒装小礼
Big box, small present.
老妈艾米我的圣诞玩笑  哇噢  哇噢
Mama Ames's Christmas fake-out. Woo woo!
这是什么
What is it?
我给你私人买了一个恒星
I bought you your very own star.
太棒了  噢
Nice! Ooh!
它在国际恒星命名管理处经过登记认证
It's recorded in the International Star Registry and everything.
我差点儿给他买了个行星的  那样可就真糗大了
I almost bought him a planet. That could have been ugly.
哇噢  谢谢你  我的甜心
Wow. Thank you, Sweetie.
嘿  老妈  看看吧
Hey, mom, check it out.
得了吧
Eh.
好了  我的礼物呢
Okay, where's my present?
呃  等等  真是  真是太喜欢你给我的礼物了
Uh, hang on. Still... still loving my present,
这礼物一定花了你不少钱吧
which must have cost you a pretty penny, yes?
老爸  送礼重在情意嘛  就别谈钱不钱的了
Dad, it's the thought that counts. Can't put a price on that.
说的是
Yes.
但你最好还是能说下多少钱
But if you could...
怎么还不见我的礼物啊
Still waiting for my present.
马上  呃
Okay, um...
呃
Uh...
算了  就这个吧
Okay, all right.
这就是  噢  瞧瞧你给我买了什么
- There we go.  - Ooh! What do we have here?
噢
Oh.
是手链啊
It's a bracelet.
噢  鲍伯  太漂亮了
Oh, Bob, it's beautiful.
你一定比我花的多多了吧
But you must have spent 10 times what I spent.
噢  现在真得谈谈钱的事儿了
Oh, now we're gonna talk prices.
呃  宝贝儿  我只是
Well, honey, I just...
真的很谢谢你  我只是
I'm very thankful, I just...
我们不是说好不花太多钱在买礼物上面吗
I thought we agreed not to spend very much.
或许你会认为我们给你的礼物更得你心
Maybe you'll find our gift a little more appropriate.
嘿  你干什么  你不能
Hey, what are you... you can't...
这是我和PJ给你买的  噢  天啦  脚踏垫啊
- This is from me and PJ! - Oh, my goodness! A foot cush?
是的
Yeah.
你们怎么知道我想要它
How did you guys know?
你们这些小鬼  说真的  我一直就想要个脚踏垫
Seriously, you guys! I have been wanting one of these forever.
噢  我的天  我跟你老爸提过一次想要的
Oh, my gosh. I mentioned it to your father once,
但我猜他跟本没放在心上
but I guess he wasn't listening.
我们放在了心上  老妈
We listen, mom.
因为我们在乎你
Because we care.
好了  来圣诞合影留念吧
Okay, time for our Christmas picture.
好的  大家都过来吧  伙计们  快过来
Okay. Let's do it, guys. Come on.
嘿  小家伙
Hey, buddy.
嘿
Hey.
噢  我们也去喽
Oh, up we go.
嘿  小家伙
Hey, buddy.
他在笑耶  多么可爱的小甜心  噢
- Smile!  - Sweetheart, oh!
十点钟方向鸽子来袭
Dove at 10:00!
呀
Ah!
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
呃  你最终还是第一次和圣诞老人合了影
Well, you finally got your first picture with Santa Claus.
这是值得纪念的一天
It was a day to remember.
但我希望你还是把我袭击圣诞老人
Although I hope you forget the part about me attacking Santa clause,
然后进监狱的部分给忘掉
and then going to jail.
或许我根本就不该在这儿提
Maybe I shouldn't have mentioned that.
嘿  查莉  呃  你最终还是第一次和圣诞老人合了影
Hey, Charlie. So, you finally got your first picture with Santa Claus.
这是我第一次在视频日记里说这件事
That I'm mentioning for the very first time.
这次的结束语  祝你好运喽  小查莉  由我来说怎么样
Hey, any chance I could say "good luck, Charlie"?
-我想试试  -哦  可以啊  当然了
- I've never said it before.  - Oh, yeah. Sure, of course.
-祝你好运喽  小查莉  -喂  你
- Good luck, Charlie.  - Hey!
咋地
Ba-bam!
嘿  今天是你人生中第一次和圣诞老人合影
Hey. You got your first picture with Santa.
祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
雪人哆雪
Snowy the Snowman, registered trademark
超级冒险乐园注册商标
of Super Adventure Land, incorporated?
你来这儿做什么
What are you doing here?
我原本想说我的头没事  谢谢关心的
My head's fine. Thanks for asking.
哦  你是在生我的气  因为我拿你的头当保龄球使
Oh, are you mad because I used your head as a bowling ball?
有点
Little bit.
是这样  我  我真的很抱歉  先进来吧
Look, I'm... I'm really sorry. Come on in.
嘿  我做点什么补偿你吧  来点曲奇怎么样
Hey, how about I make it up to you? How about some cookies?
吃我在行
I could eat.
太棒了  好  呃  你自己随意坐吧
Great. All right, well, make yourself comfortable.
我去拿曲奇  马上回来
I'll be right back.
来了  你有口福了  我这儿有巧克力薄片型的  花生奶油
Okay, so great news, we've got chocolate chip, peanut butter...
咦
Yeee!
噢
Oh!
哆雪  不
Snowy, no!
今天真够倒霉的
I'm having a bad day.